Stars and stripes flash, flash, turnin' into tacos with a side of whiplash
Fish guts on the mic, got salsa in my eye
I'm dancin' on the table like conspiracy's don't die
Be the sippin' wine, cryin' bout her ex
Top's gone flyin', it's a certified mess
She's spillin' all the tea, now the chat's on fire
Docs by a cat and her fart's gone viral
Welcome to the panel, ain't no rules to this
If you're sayin' turn back, you will not be missed
Sims in the DMs, chaos in the chat
This show's more crack than a TikTok bra
We're oversharing the live stream circus and you're already there
Welcome to the paninal
We're all gonna regret this
P.A.G.E. got simps like flies on cheese blocking blushing
Oh got someone please
Mr. B-
Still back for the work
There's no key, just an off-cam, they can love
Mods don't care, they just push and shove
Carly's cat, Kate, got a dox and list
Farded on like
Now that's a twist!
It's not a panel, it's a public breakdown
Internet therapy in a speedo gown
Keyboard warriors and washed up freaks
This is your brain after two twitch weeks
I curse my poster again
Oh, it's you. Okay. Good. Oh, yeah. I can't see you. I took a nap. Oh
Yeah, I took a nap. I was eating this shit. I was eating jack in a box. Huh?
How was it good? There you go. It was pretty good
Yeah, um, did you see chrystal marie's appearance? It was one of her legendary ones. I'm I think
He saw Tristan. This is all talking shit about me right now. She was
See if she is right now. Let me let me look at see she's all she was all funny and shit. That's a stupid
What's she mad at you?
Because she won she was like stripping for us one night for me a signal and shit
She's trying to get mad at me for it, baby. You're the one that was stripping
Well, I mean, I've seen her like in a bikini drink bikini like laying
I way had a work face
She could go look at it right now. She all mad at you
It's Joker on you see jokers on
Crystal or a Tricia Lisha. So I see her newer than we see Tricia Lisha. It's our retarded issue
Oh, I need to subscribe to her. Thank you. Tricia Lisha's t-r-i-c-i-l-i-c-i-o-u-s
Okay, yes, she is live. Let me see. Yeah, look watch. She's talking shit. You see
Such here
Melanies Melanie
Department gimmick and melody I don't know about you. Oh she was talking about me like two minutes ago
kind of sounds like Crystal Marie a little bit. Yeah.
Are they sisters? It's almost like they're sisters. Yeah, she's all mad at you.
A bit. What is it? She's showing her hot pants. Oh, she's showing these hot pants.
I just hit the chat. Yeah, two form bombs tonight that there's somebody with a lot of pictures of Black Dicks on their hard drive
but a lot of time on their hard drive is crazy
Yeah, I mean it's like they have to have that the pictures like they save it
So they're like looking at that obviously, I mean it's like kind of weird. I got my new computer
I don't watch porn on my computer
You meet you make the porno, right? Yeah, I make the porno me and my girl get the freak off for sure
Well, I'll need to be fucking watch it porn on my computer with the fuck
I pretty much have a grown it like you watch morning your computer. That's crazy. No, I don't mean I say
I don't really like porn because it's like
Doesn't really do much for me anymore. I think I'm getting too old
Hey, look at this chick Trisha. Oh my gosh, who's this person?
Wait, oh that your tattoo. I see it
I want to take my background.
You thought you were showing me your tattoo?
Um, visual.
Okay.
There we go.
See it.
Look.
Who's that person?
What?
I don't know.
Who's that?
Who the fuck is that?
I don't know.
It's Trish Delicious.
Films presents.
Oh, that's Trish Delicious.
No, it says Trish Delicious films presents.
Yep.
What?
This just happened.
It's on chat.
That's crazy.
He's a broccoli too. I don't know what that means
It's kind of weird. I don't know. It's just a very random night guys
I think Crystal Marie kind of threw me off a little bit and then the corn bomb. What are you eating?
Sandwich?
Chicken sandwich.
Chicken Sammy?
Well, I had a great burger tonight. I had still another... do I have any more coffee?
I have another small coffee over there and it's half of this one left and beer too
Just getting started guys. We're just getting started. I have a cat in my lap. I have a tricks. I have my wig handy
Hey, I don't bring my I don't use this enough. You like this thing?
It's 3 a.m. And Cali shout out to you, but it is 3 a.m. 3 a.m. guys
It's a witching hour 3 a.m. It's like a it's the best hour
Best hour but let people wake up in the middle of the night at 3 a.m. Oh, it is all horny as shit drinking Bud Light
Yeah
Is there is there is there old ladies drinking blood blood light in the chat shout out
Any old ladies drinking blood light in the chat that are horny? Maybe some of you know Chris crystal kept referencing these 90 year old
Man that are 90 year old people that were like assassins or something our goons. She said I
Still know I'm drinking but like at 3 a.m. That's some witch shit. Yeah, it is some witch shit
But I'm trying to E and J bottles
And I have my I have my Cobra staff protecting me from
Bro, where did I see that what movie the somebody has a Cobra stuff? Maybe the mummy or god
It's Egypt. Oh, but like Aladdin or something. It's too far. I was like a Jackie Chan movie or something. I go. Yeah. Yeah
My god
Let me see is anybody in the chat talking midnight. Okay, sick. So the two of you constantly have sex off stream
Glow
That I don't have sex with signal. He's still fat
Yeah
So someone thinks that you're talking about backstage sex with men, but I don't think so like I don't think he's doing that
He went maybe we're gonna experiment if you can ever come down here, but he says yeah, he says you do it backstage
Oh say that just he's just trying to make me jealous come on
Nah, I don't have sex with him.
What is that?
What's that?
Oh, it's a thing.
There's a thing sticking up behind you.
It looks like a penis head, but it's not.
The only time I had sex backstage was with Psyche.
Oh, yeah.
We did that once.
And he saw everything.
I mean, everything.
Yeah, why did you why did you disappear so fast when I was I showed you?
You don't show me anything well, I got people around me as well
But it was supposed to have a threesome with your wife and then all of a sudden you disappeared and it was just me and
See and I don't want to be with him. It was just you and say you were disappointed. He was over there
He was there taking screenshots
On the dark web
I'm proud of what I got, you know
She's sick says you guys have this thing where you tie your hands behind your head and then bump your bumps
The bumps mean like like bumps like you're
Bumps are cocaine. Yeah. Oh
Like like your belly is belly bumps. I don't know midnight so weird. Hey midnight. How are you?
Me and signal do a lot of cocaine. I'll tell you that
Well, that will lead to doing bumps
Um, especially cocaine you'll do like tons of lines up toilet seats and because it doesn't last very long actually
Yo, he's trying to say cocks nicely. Okay. Yeah, you don't have to say you don't have to say nicely
You can say cock. I like the word cock
Right, or you can say gaio like pico de gaio means like look at my cock, right pico me
Mn believes everything that sig says. Yeah, I mean I don't what does that say in your arm?
What does that say?
This one. Yeah, what does that say? This is rugged. Oh, do you see mine? Look at mine. I have a tattoo like that
Look at my arm. Oh, yeah, your arm looks gay
Excuse me. Yeah, well, I'm gay, but look, well, this is part of this looks gay, too. Look
Okay. Oh that was dope. What the fuck is that?
That looks like some KKK suit. What's that?
It's just an interesting symbol
And I also, oh shit. Is that like the hem the hem symbol?
You know, it's a cult symbol and then I have on this one. I think that I have Horus right here
Oh, that's pretty dope. Thank you. That's cool
Ilya you're not like that blue one that blue was hard. Thank you. It's called and it's it's the blue is it's called Dodger blue
That's the blue is cold so fuck the Dodgers
Man with cancer falling there must be I got the 300 on it. This is cold
We do cold right here. Yeah, the 300 glow cold or is it your cold?
blow
Since the cult of psyche is looking to like branch out to other cults and like you know affiliate and stuff
If we can do some business
Yeah, I have my my
Covers it actually turns into a real snake if I like remember the right magic words
But I haven't my girls all mad at me. She's like, oh sweet
Because you want you to go to bed in a hotel right now. Go come with
Get it, but I'm trying to like live right now, you know, okay
So midnight says like I come on the internet. I'm such a nice girl and that Ilya starts giving me shit
Look at my shirt, bro. Alright, just take it all off. Just take it off. It feels like food all over it
I need to wear a new shirt
Just take it off. All right
Oh, here we go. Yes
This is what the show is about guys. Yeah
Yeah, that's dead. Yeah
Whoa, I like it
I like it. It's uh, it's look so good
You're gonna he's shut up. Well, well, you know, I guess he's gonna go to bed with his wife and stuff, but
Thank you for that treat. See that's what that's the kind of poor mom. I'm not a poor mom
It's like just just a sexy Latino
Nice
Love it. Oh so so hot
Do you have any more tattoos? What does that say? It's oh at the LP flip or is it out flow? What does it say?
Did it say
Bp is something club
What is that? This is a club wear. Oh, you're putting your shirt back on a pro club. Is it a pro club?
No
Well, nice you're wearing black. Do you like my green? I'm wearing green. I have the green goddess behind me. She's a
He's not with a female yes, he is
a fake average streaming for
40 hours now
Really? We've been asleep yet?
Yeah, I've been asleep early. I've been asleep earlier. You did a sleep stream or you just
Like turn off the camera ship, but I've been live
So I've been live for let me see
Let me check my rumble.
I've been live for, uh...
Ah, fuck.
Wait a minute.
I'll tell you.
Are you live on kick or twitch?
I'm rumble, my boy
Okay
I ain't live on twitch, you can't go to fuck
I mean, I can seem to rumble too
Man, okay bro, you ain't got to
No, I can if I want to, but it takes an extra step
And so it's easier for me to do it
Dang, don't hurt my boy, you ain't got to do shit for me
I'm gonna say, oh yeah
I have 475 views
Okay
I mean for tonight
It's for two days. Okay. That's pretty good. That's good for a rumble
I think because I know like Chris K says he gets like 20 25 views or something
So tell you buddy, I'm really on here. I have 18 people in the chair right now
Hey, shout out to the real chat. That's right. Yeah
Hey, shout out to the three yeah chat. Hell yeah
Yeah, imagine people typing at 3 a.m. That's cool, but you got motion
No, I can't even type right now. I'm just
Cain oh
Look at how cute tricks is look at this cat
Tricks. Yeah, that's tricks right there. He's sleeping. Oh, that's your that's the name of your cat tricks. Yeah tricks. Yeah
You have a brother named magic and magic had like a little white paws
Call the magic and he's tricks, but
Magic took off
Here's the North people no, are you gonna say hi? Why are you sleeping on the table like that?
Look at all the money
That'd be hot if you just like
Throw it all over my naked body. I'd love that. Oh, look at the kitty cat
Kitty oh, yeah, yeah, oh
Look at the white cat, I love little white cats. Oh, it gets the cats counting money now to cats rich
Okay, I have one money than me and that cat spoiled
of the
other white the white cast and Luna
of the girls only have girls
Two girls so it's me my girlfriend and her three cats, and they're all girls
These are you are outnumbered now right on the alpha male. Yes
Exactly. You're the only male in the house. Yeah, what a estrogen balancing out, right? Yeah, you see that
You see that why I can't have a conversation sometimes my girl. She's just don't get it. I'm like a good
native relaxed
Cuz I am the only one swinging a dick around here. I like that my shit
Well, you're like the man in the house, right?
And they rely on you and I really hold it and I really hold it down
I swear to God. I bet you have like a firearm and all kinds of stuff. I work hard. I play hard
Nice don't question my shit because I'll make it happen. Okay. I don't question you
Are you good, psyche?
You good, bro. Okay. Do you hear Christian Marie talking earlier? She was pretty wild. Oh, Christian Marie was wrong. Yeah
Yeah, I see that it was she was saying that why don't you want to repeat it or I'll get in big trouble by Christine, but
She was saying that Bozzie has rabies and you know crystal Marie or she said Christine has
Hired or she's hired 90 year old goons to push Christine on the stairs. I don't I don't know Christine. Just what is yeah, just be careful
You know, you don't you don't never know it's
Missy oh that's all I know
I doubt
You're 30 or 30 to 20 still 20
My god, how old are you 20 something? I'm just doing my 20s. Okay. I'll tell you that. Well, I'm way older than like an old man
No, I'm not 21 22. That's for sure
Okay, you're late 20s, okay
I'm in my mid 40s 44 and 45 this time. I'm at there. Oh
They're they're weed
Or your asthma asthma. Oh, it's every bit. Yeah, it's your inhaler. I did too much. No, it's my boy
Okay, I'm smoking awesome shit. You see me smoking as the when I barely started hopping on a shit
You see me is it not a nice oxide like not sure it's outside like a nitrous. Yeah, you know what?
Boy a popper a popper. I used to get a cracker from the tank from the tank. Let's see what the
Fucking you said these things called if you get the little mini tanks
And then we buy this thing called a cracker and you put in the cracker
We'll put a balloon on it and then you sit there with the balloon and then it's like
Hey, I was retarded after a while
That's the most shit, man. Yeah, that's the most shit
Have you ever seen um scribbles that he's got him scribbles irl. He has like
I've heard of him, but I've never watched him. I'll tell you that
Well, sometimes he has a balloon. He's holding a balloon and he's just like
He's serious. He's like serious to camera art.
And Dale.
And Dale is like dumb dumb, right?
Yeah, y'all are stupid, man.
But uh, yeah, Ghost basically taught me how to do that.
Coming down. Yeah, I have the thing is I have a full tank right here in my cabinet and I won't smoke that shit no more
I'm I keep that shit for a trophy. I'm like don't hit it
Well, in case you ever had to have to like do some home dental work
It will be very handy, right? If I need to blow somebody up. Yeah, I'll be like
Well, now just kidding
hopefully
Have those new cabinets to come down
So there's my accusations the terrible accusations being made in the chat. Let me see
Accusations is crazy. They're saying you have they're saying you're you can't breathe well from having sex with females
That's why he has sex with sex with females. That's the dope you already
And then he says he's one of the worst rumors in Riverside, and that's not a compliment. I'm not from Riverside
Your boyfriend's here your boyfriend's here. Hold on a second. Oh
See those here. I think but I can't let him up until I see him say show me on camera
If you don't know not here real safe here once again, we ain't got a dick like that
Oh, it was a fake say it was a fake sig. Oh my god. Yes, I'm not here. I was caught me three times tonight. It's crazy
Give up your lighters pink
Yeah, you don't you're like Matt you're like secured up your mask. I need to have a pink lighter. I'm not I'm not all
fruity and shit, by the way
I mean, I wouldn't have a pink web, but you know my letter is um
It has a fox on it. You would have a peak lighter
I'm gay enough. I don't need like the gay the pink the pink letter. There you go. You're just you're answering my question
You're asking me your own question. I don't like
It's just like for a straight guy. It's like confident for a gay guy. It's just like look for a lighter
You need a lighter right now to hit a ball. Go look for it. I have it
It's Fox later. No, it wasn't that one go look for one. What would you find?
I have a panther one I think or some other kind of cat because this is this is who my girl has
If I go look for a lighter, I'll find my girl ship
Oh, you're saying here's my other lighter. It has a girl is like my my manager my like little
site, uh
What do you call that?
Your business advisor your
Secretary whatever you want to call this
perfect
So whatever I need I got in hand. He's like hey, go get me some shit
Do you like that picture of me?
That's you that don't look like you wish doesn't that looks kind of mean
But I didn't look at that then it's like that nah
Not even that one. I don't think me. Okay. How about well this one
Right here. I should have another how about this one?
All right, that was chill that little that list here. Yeah. Oh, that's that's actually somebody else
I do have a picture of me see gallery yeah, but go to my gallery. Look at this picture. You look this one
It's kind of going slow. Let me see. Where is this picture? Okay? Well, oh here
Cut em up. I'm a really cut em up. Oh
Now I'm making Peters frozen. Okay. Pull up. I'm a pull up
Anything
So we psyche cat daddy
Yeah
Cuz you own cats. Yeah, you said cat daddy, huh? Yeah
Yeah, meow, meow. Oh, yeah, look at this picture. What do you think of this one?
Oh, that was I can't where was that where was that was a redondo. Yeah
She pulled up. Yeah
She's ill like that. Yeah, it's chill like that. Yeah, she's awesome
We went to Hollywood the next day. She drove me to Hollywood. Oh, what he drove you to Hollywood. That's the long ass drive
Yeah, it's like 30 40 minutes
Which I think she was like she like worked around there's or
psyche seagull. Yeah, and then I made like a
another
I made a kind of copy of it, I made a copy of it, that's really cool if I have that.
Oh look it, there's GT, okay, where's my freaking files?
That's cool as well.
Yeah.
And she left, she flew out again?
She drove out and then she drove back and then we have the same birthday and so I think
we're planning on hanging out on our birthdays.
Bro, hit me up.
Well done.
That'd be fun.
Yeah, so here's the one.
I can pay for the drinks.
What do you think of this one?
See what do you think of that?
I'm not stingy.
That one looks legit.
Better than the other ones you were trying.
That's for sure.
Little bit more stylized, but uh, yeah, we had a great time. Yeah, I guess
That shit just looks like
Oh if you left oh
Um, I would mean that she will not I love I love Alex. She's awesome
Crazy, I would never think that she would go outside like that
Well, um, she's met a lot of streamers. She's met with a lot of streamers. Um, she's met
Um
Tommy James she's met Cheeto scheme at yeah cheeto. I think she met ski mask Andy
I think she met I
Think you make you you all that's candy is crazy. That's like the Sin City, dude. Yeah, and
I don't know if she met Chris K, but I
Wondered if Chris K is gonna come and do chatter bait with me. That'd be interesting
He said he's down
Yeah, he is that Chris K's there
Yeah, I could tell you that
Well, that'd be pretty fun
Because it's like I'd be interesting to like hook up with somebody this panel verse right man. I said man. I got no respect
Oh, oh
Midnight, I don't care. I mean that's just a hater. Come on. Yeah flex. Let's off
I didn't know I looked like this, but I guess you're so good
Like shirt, I think it's the shirt
Well, I was wearing a wife beater and speedos on Lord Vader's
And yeah, he asked me to dance and stuff and I kept doing it and then now he's asking to
Nothing, I mean there was no music you just like you just oh he did put on music
Hey, come here dance and I was like
To no music is crazy
And then now everyone's saying he's gay
I think he might be by curious. I don't know he's telling you to dance on history and everything. Come on, bro
Yeah, well, it was fun
And then he like but then he got mad at everybody like rain and JT and like Ziggy over jealous
They were all jealous. Yeah, he's already yelling at everybody and he was the only one in the chat
He's like, oh, he was like yelling at people in the chat and I was like, wow
I feel sometimes
so
This is fun. This is I feel like this is like my steering wheel. Yeah.
That's a staff. I've never heard of somebody having a staff. Yeah, I got staff.
Um, I think I only seen like karate Asian movies with a stab. The dude has a stab.
He knows how to fight all cool and shit. Yeah.
But this was actually a good deal. I got on probably team 420 bucks, which is a very good deal. What? Yeah, good craftsmanship, huh?
It's really nice heavies and stuff
metal
Oh, yeah, team has a really great stuff. You especially like the glasses
No, you like these glasses pink ones. I got my ring light
I'm seeing my big ring light, like bigger than the hand, look.
It is a big one, like they have quality stuff.
I see a face in there, I see a face right there, is that Bloody Mary or Maria?
Oh yeah.
Hey Wild German lady, how are you?
Yeah, we're chillin' ready.
How are you Wild? This is my new channel.
My girl's calling me, let me see.
Okay, well, you go, go to your lady.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
Midnight. Oh, no, I mean, I didn't mean to do that home. I was trying to do somebody else for the guy, bro
I thought you were all high up
Nah, I'm I well, I don't have weed right now, but I'm yeah, I'm chill right now. It's this other person
Okay, thank you. Somebody else got it. Oh, yeah
This is for my girl. I'm gonna go hydrate her my day. We'll take care. We'll take care
Yeah, anybody else might come up on the piano before
Does he put a ring a light I can't dream together
You know let's say
Who said I'm live money for 20 or yeah, stop the look crazy thoughts
Yeah, drink your water
You look like you're wearing a shirt or something.
You know what I'm saying?
The reasoning 69 is saying hi to your glow and uh...
The reason...
Is there a plant? Where did you put the plant on?
The really bad plant?
I did. It stood there to me.
You started doing that shit.
You were doing that shit all day all night. Let's go over it.
I'm fighting you.
Yeah
Yeah, because you were like where daddy eat nothing, right? I just ate my chicken sandwich right now
Yeah, but my tacos are right there all over my keyboard is
Yeah, I ain't gonna cat
Hey, we finished all the drink
You don't got no you don't got no drink stairs
You don't want no more water?
so
So I'll be okay. I just smoke some weed. I'll smoke some weed and I'll be good
On snapchat you can like
iPad me
I see I'm trying to yeah, I can uh, I can generate
Well, why is that one? I
Can be an iPad mini. I got it probably
2021 or something and so it's kind of like a little bit. Oh, it's the older model. Oh
I
With the SIM card, huh the best I pan mini six with the SIM card is the best
Oh my god, it's making scary pictures of me shit. I love this is good
It's like it's like these AI swap pictures
But it's like so it's like you pick a picture and then it will like swap my face onto it
But it's making them look kind of insulting. There's a lot of my
I'll show you let's see if I can do it says kind of cool though
No way a fake signal try to join is crazy
Let's see
Okay, now check this out. Oh, wow, I look really cool. Well, this one's scary. This one is like does not look like me. Does it?
Oh, like that one mean what does that mean?
I don't know, I don't know what that one is, but let's see.
Oh.
See it.
Oh, that was good.
It's my face on all these.
Then you want to make do you tell it to make your eyes that big to look at this one?
No, I know it just makes it like that. See it's like has a bunch of
Format that was a good one
Yeah, that was like too
There it is, there it is.
Oh, here I am as a football player.
I see it now.
As a football player, that is a football player.
How about that?
Pretty hot.
I see it.
Hell yeah.
Oh, that won't eat it.
I'm like, oh, oh my god.
That looks like you in a forest with the iPad.
Hey, guess what we have?
We have a guest here.
I'm going to have to make sure it's a real guest.
Let me see.
Yeah, bro.
Is it the real guest?
Yes, it is.
I have to sneeze. Oh my gosh. I don't even know what it's doing, but I do have to sneeze. Okay. God bless you
Oh, look at this one. I feel like I did. Oh my gosh, psyche. I love you so much. I hope you're doing good
I'm good. Look how sassy I'm in this picture
You look spider-man
Kind of oh here's me as a nerdy up nerd on my wedding day
Oh my gosh, look how handsome you've always been the most handsome
That me look at me. Oh, that's definitely not you, but you know, you're the most handsomest
How's that one?
Very handsome
Yeah
Oh, man, it wasn't scary though. Yeah, that one that was like skibbity
Stop it like you stop. Oh, this one ran bull
Broke that down you could write this bull psyche. Let's do it here. You're running out all year
Claymation here
You know before I was like on this platform
I got like a bunch of TV show like I've been on like a bunch of TV shows and
Like I've gotten like a lot of roles and stuff and it's very small
but
Like for whatever reason in my area like even like the most beautiful women. It's crazy
They're they're always a lot of beautiful women around you. They just hate me
Because you're beautiful and you know beautiful people like get insecure
Yeah, they they go to war for their looks. I believe that
Here's me as a you know, my my family always says it's a super funny like how they do that like like
And and it is like what they like the things that cat that
Christine Christine tries to say that I'm this crazy person. I make up all these stories
I I have all these things in my mind about her and
She literally talks about me every single day and I have
I'm not on my own term. It's a different
Different consideration different lawyer different state
That's representing me against her
What are you talking about? Like what is she talking about? Let's see
The seat of in Florida. I'm not in Florida. I
Didn't know people in Florida
But I have two representatives in Florida now
I
Have some niggas to in Florida for sure. Well listen I
Got a 90-year-old representative is about to go over to the next that's crazy
You're you're wild and you need representatives in Florida. It's kind of wild Chris. I'm not from Florida. No, that bitch is
That's what I'm saying
Yeah
She wants to get checked a flight me out I'll go slap that bitch
Well that Christine bitch will you slap her for me, please? Thank you flight me out to Florida?
I'll I'll tell her what it is 300 glue. What do you think about this woman right here? I will fly you out
I will fly her
Crazy, that's me
Protect you we got it. We're not flying you out there to get
Make sure you're protected buddy
I mean, we can't just fly you out there. Yeah. Don't understand that. Yeah, I do. I'm just kidding. It's just
I should have been saying shit like that, but it's funny to me.
You know, it's really unfortunate for me because she is like, she pays everybody to say, like, it's so insane.
I
Have a social media lawyer on the case on where on what platform
Unvoking on fucking Christine since the last year since she's been following me
She's obsessed because
You know her
Son is a criminal and he wanted to fuck me. Oh, she
So this is where this all started is that Christine son wanted to fuck me and he had a baby and we didn't know that
Oh shit, but did you fuck him?
No, I would never fuck a loser like that
No, no, her fucking stupid ass son is just a little I was like her son
Well girls can fuck whoever they want to fuck but doesn't me ask her with all that bullshit
But can you tell Christine that she's a low life or old or low?
Have you ever seen her face?
Yeah, she said she's not even
Come to find out. She's not even she's just like a couple of years. Maybe one or two years older than me. Oh
my god
So she's got like a like she had a kid when she was like 14 or something 13
She's your age. She looks like it's about 17 years old though. Yeah, she looks 70 years old
And she's had a lot of plastic surgery and she's literally my age
She's younger than fucking beta dude. Oh my god, she's in our 40s
In your 40s and 20 25 was crazy
Yeah, that bitch looks washed. She looks like she got hit with a fucking
Bunch
With an ugly thing she got hit with ugly dogs in her face
No, that ugly dog Fonzie that fucking and then she said that her fucking
Do you was trying to say that I had mental disorder? What is mental disorder to you?
Do you think having a fucking animal?
No matter what age it is and had rabies
Yeah, that's bad
You think not
Getting rid of the dog. It's a part of life. Okay. It's a part of life things die
You're not gonna put other people at risk of life, but no, she's a fucking nurse and she says she knows better and she
Apparently I have 10 fucking people my fucking hand and
She is zero, but she still makes zero fucking decisions
wise
so I don't know one of my fucking retarded as well and
She likes to say I have 10 fucking people mad
One of my retard fucking people and your fucking head would never fucking
Sit around and have fucking rabies and sit like it's nothing. You stupid disgusting
Hore your growth. I hope you rotten hell and you should fucking not be around
Yeah, that's crazy
W
I'm just not sure where to think right now
Well, that's the W Swanky. That's called a hole. No, that's disgusting
It's called disgusting
Well, I say W because I understand what you're saying. I see what you're saying you do
She was saying that her animal had rabies and then she was not gonna
That's what this means right here psyche
Okay, you speak crystalline
Hey crystal
Sir
How's your night? What are you drinking? Oh
I've been doing good. Oh, thanks for asking actually, you know a lot of people don't ask me
Is this a picture of pristine?
Well, thank you for asking, you know, I cleaned up
That her that Christine
Looks like Christine that is Christine is that Christine? Yeah
There's some selfies
That's much much. Yeah, I'm not I'm not in there for sure
No, I'm I'm sorry guys, you know, I really wish I could be nicer
You good girl
No, it really hurts my feelings though, dude, I'm so nice
There it is
I'm so nice in real life, but they just won't let me be that person, you know
So when I bet I go to my grandma's house
And she fucks with me
It's like don't act too don't say too much don't say too much crazy shit. I'll be like all right
Yeah, I understand. You know, that's exactly it like listen. I like I
Have the same feeling, you know, it's like you don't go and like that's what like I wish people had that same thought
Yeah
So me and Cheeto go hang out soon, I got the DMs from my phone
The DM what do you say I can't hear
He said he was gonna hang out with Cheeto soon. Yeah me and Cheeto
We talked to each other every day
Let me find my phone
When you know you might have gotten my
Okay
I said is what I said and you might not like what I say
Sometimes but it's the truth and sometimes you're not deal with it
so
When you go to the area that you're going with you're gonna have to fucking deal with it
Just like Christine when she walks out of her house, that's why she will never walk out of her house again
She's gonna have to deal with that
Never again. Yeah, that's what I'm saying. She ain't never walking out of her house again. I won
I won
What did you win?
It's just have to turn
Oh my god
So how are we doing tonight? Oh my gosh
I miss you so much
Honestly, I think your hair like looks so handsome. We look so handsome
Yes with your hair like pulled back out of your face
Thank you so much
I
Yes, you look so handsome with it pulled out of your
Thank you
I think I'm looking a little bit better late. Yeah a little bit like I've been eating a lot of McDonald's and it's actually been good for my skin
Oh, I don't know about the McDonald's situation. I don't know about the skin situation
Well, I do look a little bit I do look kind of good though, I say I'm well
I can't tell because of that, you know that filter II
I'm not using a filter
But I'm saying
That you are a handsome man, and I love I think we're all beautiful
Love your hair and like tied back. I mean just saying thank you. Yeah, it's like a little like a yeah
I it looks so handsome. You look like very handsome. Thank you
Yeah, I'm actually got a lot of confidence since I started streaming because it's like I never used to like be able to I was very
Used to be very like paranoid when I was outside and like didn't think anyone thought I was good-looking and now like a lot of people
Have said I'm good with you. So now you are so attractive
especially
Like you're naturally attractive
Which is so much more than like just attraction
like you have like
Just like me like people were to come up to me people love me, but
Not on here, you know, everybody hates me on here, of course. No, I love you
I know
I like play up like I just like it kind of silly because it's a show and stuff and I try to like, you know
Be funny and it's like sometimes not for you, but I'm a cancer dude. I'm very sensitive. Yeah. Yeah
Oh, I cancer is the rule by the moon. So they yeah, they like they love their environment
They love their home. They love their shell, but and they're sent they're very sensitive because it's the moon
And it's like the water move by the water. Yeah, the moon is cool
I fuck with the moon I'm also cancer crystal so as I understand they're a little crabby sometimes they're crabs right they're crabs
No, it's very emotional. Yeah, it's a crab sign. So it's like yeah
The moon always goes through the phases like the different phases and so it's like that like just like the emotions too
I'm a capricorn. It's trying to help people
It's more trying to help people
Because the moon is like a the moon is very nurturing force too, right? It's like a mother kind of force. It's like uh
Yeah, I get like a lot of shit for trying to help you.
I get the fucking wrath.
I get no love for hate.
I'll get no love for hate.
I'm like, I'm like.
People like I give them love they give me hate. I recognize that you are loving and I I
I'm so I am I'm I really truly sorry if I ever your feelings or if I was like sarcastic or anything like that
It's fine. It's it happens every day. Everybody always says the same thing. It's so weird
Serious try to put something like they trying to make me
Turtle weaponize my talents
Right because
We all we have because I have a personality and I can talk right so they weaponized it now
They're saying that I have multiple personalities and I was like is this I
Even was questioning myself dude
After I had all these fucking supposedly people and then I was asking and
Then that's when we are gonna get these people
Locked up like fucking
You know these people should not be doing what they're doing like
Like a Christine or a spunky. Unfortunately. She just got mixed in
But yeah, this is looked into big doctors big huge
Big huge are looking into them and they're gonna see what's going on with them
Yeah, I hope I hope spunky is not involved with spunky, please
Unfortunately she got involved
So she might even be questioning her own. Yeah, she might lose
Who even knows what they're gonna do, you know, these people are senators. I
Don't know. Yeah
When it gets into politicians it gets really complicated
They're powerful, right donkey punch you there's a donkey. Yeah, you donkey punch me a donkey punch you. Yes
That's what you bought a punch you said he said I bought a donkey punch you
Thing I want but her name. It's her name. I'm sorry
We're trying not to do it of that hard. We're trying to make it more just where
Where people can't do that like to me. I'm like what they did to me like should not be done
Do you think Christina's had a ride a donkey?
No, but she needs to be in a psych ward
We need to get her locked up in a psych ward. She needs to be in a psych ward
She shouldn't be around children or animals 50 150 like a 75 year old woman. No, I'm not sure
Yeah, something like that
Okay, Abon you get donkey in your name before I knew you oh my god, so we got it. We are gonna like
We got the people I
Can't be involved cuz I probably
Yeah, I don't want to get involved. Um, yeah, just if you're gonna like go after Christine with the
I got a nine-year-old goon
in a right around here
a nine-year-old man
in Florida
he's a man
an old dude
easy, right
But it's like isn't he like kind of a slow assassin or like goon or whatever. He's like do you have a cane or something?
Well, well, you would think so buddy. He is with FBI. So
Like a vampire
He's like a 90 year old goon with the FBI in Florida
Looking just looking for fucking Christine to fall down the steps so he can or just waiting for like
so he can
That's right
anyways
300 glue left, but so it's just you and me. Hey, um
Do you want to say something to the chat or?
I'm just kidding. I'm kidding about no like but it could be like it could be it could be
It could be it couldn't be okay, but but I'm telling you that it's not somebody in my head, okay, like these people
I'm just should just be in silly in
But I got people that will do that for me in Florida
In her fucking area, but just by the way
Can you imagine what if I'd be so embarrassed if I got attacked by a 90 year old person and they pushed me on this
I'd be just goon a 90 year old goon in a wheelchair by the way. Okay. Yeah, we understand. I'm honest as we understand so I
Backed up. Yeah, so my main and I was still timed out. You're fine midnight. You're in the chat
Yeah, I got a 90-year-old goon waiting for Christine to fuck up at her fucking next door fucking app
Or what is it called?
The next door app
Well
Yeah, kind of like a next door app, but for old people
like
Like next next retirement home. Yeah, we're next retirement app. Yeah. Yeah, I got the 90 year old. That's about to fuck you up, bitch
She's on her fucking ass. She's ready and it's maybe a man. Maybe a woman
Like yeah, it's like it's the element of surprise. You can ever maybe it's maybe me. Maybe it's it. Maybe it's a transgender
Yeah, exactly
Yeah, remember how she went so hard on fucking fucking our girl
Flirty like we did not deserve see you guys always want to forget though like the things like our
core things that really just
Turn me completely off on people
And I don't when I get turned off on people. I just like don't like them ever again
But you've hated me before and you come back to like me. So maybe there's hope for some people
Well, I you are rude to me, but I
Never got turned off by you
But I don't I don't have mallet like really I don't have any mallets in my heart. I
Don't yeah, I didn't feel that. Yeah, you know what I mean. I didn't feel that
Hate and the
If you ever you know, you know, you know, these people are really hating me on me like really hard
and
Like you understand. Yeah, I felt a lot of hate from people too. So
I definitely get that I relate and it's it sucks
But you know what there's people that love me too and that makes it okay that like they like surround me
The love surrounds me more. Yeah, the thing is is that like us we actually have love
People like Christine has zero love
Right because she was just dropped me like a hot potato like she just like and she's like I don't say he's mentally ill
And he just wants to fish tacos and dick and all this kind of stuff. How rude but she's completely insane
And her kids don't even want to talk to her and she abuses her fucking family members
Well, aren't they all adults though? I mean
Yeah, they are all adults and she still acts like their children imagine
Would never want like I always said that that that's why she hates me so much is that like
She is like so mean to that lady that
The woman that the father of her
Brian killed kids
She's like oh, oh
He doesn't have he's got
Oh, he's gonna take his kids trick-or-treat and then that woman that guy like somebody was like
Are you going to go treating with your knee or with your grandkids and she was like
They have they have a father not like they have a mother and father or whatever she was like
And I just want to smack that old cunt in her face for that woman. I want to smack her right in the head
Just say shut up and don't disrespect that lady you don't know her and your son's probably a piece of shit like she is
The son that wanted to see with you are you talking about her her son's a prisoner her son's an ex-personer
I don't know. He might have I don't know. He might have been an ex
Somebody that wanted to get without he's from Missouri
I'm kind of famous in Missouri in a weird way
Why would you do Missouri?
Well, I'm a model. My brothers are musicians famous ones. Yeah, what kind of music comes out of Missouri?
Blues and metal. Oh cool
Blues the blues the blues and metal music
Fucking metal like a motherfucker. We will rip somebody's heads off
And that's why I like saying that I don't rip and had somebody's heads off
Just listen to metal music and smack in somebody the fucking thing
Well, I mean it's like if you're listening to music you shouldn't be like fighting. It's sort of a mosh pit or something, right?
Christine's only yeah, that's what it is about
It's about a mosh pit
Mosh pit. Hey, when's the last concert you went to?
Oh, man, I haven't been to a concert actually I haven't been to a concert in a while
The like the main things I've been to lately is like games
I'm going to games lately
Baseball games or football Oh
Oh, yeah football baseball. Yeah
Pickleball soccer hockey. I love hockey
About yeah, we have everything here in Missouri. We have game central
We have we are the fucking rollers of fucking games. You don't even know our fucking city. I love my city
And so you get out a lot of the sports events, that's cool. I haven't been
Last the sports event I went to is a dodger game, I think
And it's you know, it's not about the game itself. It's a camaraderie
And that's what I always like die on is the camaraderie and I don't have that and not like I always wished
We could have that here and you guys have it with the people that pay, but I'm not gonna pay for camaraderie
Yeah, I I own camaraderie. Yeah, we should be free, right? It should be just be like yeah, I own camaraderie
This should be this is a natural
Thing that some people don't have
Yeah, it's like you can't buy it
You cannot buy it. Yeah, and that's what like some of these people that really hate on me and say that I have multiple
personalities don't understand that
They don't know about gaming they don't know about shit and they just
They just never made a dollar in their fucking life
Like she's um, she fucking got with this fucking guy, right?
This truck driver that she took advantage of this fat fucking low life, right?
This drug drug addict low life. This is what Christine got going on
She took advantage of some drug fucking low life that had kids
and said that she was like raising.
Now she wants to like pretend that they're her,
that they're her kids.
Half of these kids aren't even hers.
She just babysitting?
Remember, I thought she had chickens.
That she's like-
Yeah, she's just controlling people.
Even that guy that she marries kids.
Yeah.
He doesn't even like her and
She's she's on the her outs
And she's mad at me because nobody likes
Well, she said like that she thinks that people are gonna like think that she's gonna like unalive them
Like if they like, you know come into the hospital, they think she's gonna be like
Well, we do have to actually check that out. We really need to because did you not see what she said?
Oh, she says crazy stuff. She does. She does, you know, I just she actually in its clip
Yeah, she said
That if I was to ever go to her hospital
She would not take care of me
That's wrong. It's like against the Hippocratic Oath, which says we have to take care of her.
So, so she's saying, so what is she saying? Do you understand what I'm getting at?
Yeah, okay, I wouldn't trust you.
And then she's saying that I have multiple personalities just to cover up for her dumb shit.
What do I even have multiple personalities about who am I like will you want me to who else am I?
Well, I remember this lady on Lisa Jordan is going with a lot of law
She thought she was Albert Einstein as well as like some other famous people and then she like
Yeah, you do have the reasoning singing of a beautiful why never I never thought that but
But I will tell you that mine Anna
Is poor she spoke Portuguese only Portuguese
And we went to this tribal
council thing and it was fucking awesome and
You know that
She passed long ago, you know
Well, she passed when she was like at 90. I think she was 94 but
And then my a pop has when he was a hundred and two oh listen one life
They told me these things we talked right and it was so weird that I never spoke the same language we always spoke
And they are always gonna protect me and
My higher-ups are better like that like they say like higher-ups and people attacking people like mine are
actually real and
Mine are I seen it I seen I seen
Indian stuff I seen rituals I seen it
Okay, I I seen it. They addressed it. They they dressed up in uniform
We've seen it. Okay, so these are the people that are protecting me
Yeah, like powerful people
Hey, we have got a first will go. Oh, this is the big that's not the real first one goes. I don't believe it
So this is a really cool app. I don't need to see how let me see if I can put behind me
It's making me all kinds of like different
You see it. It's making me all kinds of different time travel. Let's see. I can do it when the 80s now
See I'm in the 80s then I'm in the 90s
And then I'm in the 2000s. Oh my god, and then the 2010s in no way
And that's yeah
It's a Google. It's a Google app. It's pretty cool. Oh, that is so crazy
And then I have what's this one do this one does
headliner
Tap to take the stage. Oh, oh, that is so cool
This song this is snapchat. It's pretty funny. It's pretty cool. Yeah
Well, you're really handsome. I think you're pretty handsome on all of them
You I
Love some of the different looks I can yes, you are yes, you are handsome and
Don't let people fucking tell you're not you know like
Well, I probably don't know how much longer I have of being handsome, but maybe I'll be a nice-looking older man though, you know, like
Silver Fox they say I'd like to be a silver fox. Well, they say that
That you lose your looks, but you know, I just made 88 dollars an hour
modeling
And they want to talk about my looks
You're beautiful you have a great bod you have a great face
I mean don't let anybody tell you anything different. You'd be confident yourself just like you said to me, right?
Says they say you need a penis to apply crystal. What does that mean? Oh my gosh
You need a penis to apply says crystal is gay the dudes just do it around here when they won't be a pro by 300 glow
I know I don't know what they're talking about. They say they mean. Oh, yeah
Can I have a translator please in the room? I mean I say I don't understand anybody tonight. I mean
Was it was that I heard a bizarre man in your house
Oh for a ride that wasn't my house. That was your bones. I heard my voice
I'll tell you what I bet 1 million that Chris summary could clean up on porn because she would make dudes suck blooper
Dude suck blooper
Okay, and it says too far of Anna. Okay guys
Are these jokes
No, I'm not talking to them. Not you Chris crystal is
You are you are you are
No
Do you understand how I can only take so much? Yeah
Fuck this world's full of bullshit and it's like, you know and people like you know
Like they think that I'm like this crazy person. I'm just trying to be myself, dude
I'm just trying out fun and being myself and you
I'm just trying to and you know what I'm not I try not to like hurt anybody and I try not hurt any feelings or try to like
I try to like you know
I know that everybody uses me as like a weapon. They weaponize they use me as like a weaponize me
But don't I do I wouldn't do that. I just like let you up when you want to come up
I don't I don't like try to like well you like you said
Not trying to use against Chris Chris Christine. I really am not you brought her up on your own
I I I don't know what you're gonna bring
I think it's that the whole thing is we don't know where you're gonna say next Chris
So you're unpredictable you're chaotic and I like that about you. I like chaos and
I don't think you're harm harming anybody, but
You never know what you're gonna say
It's called yeah, I just I just feel very uh
be down well I don't want to be like how can I make you not like how can I help
you know that I'm not trying to like contribute to that or like I don't know
I don't want to make you feel bad I just want to know you don't well it's just
that you don't help like it's I know you're just trying to be like
Sometimes I try to be funny like a funny host so it to entertain but you don't help
But you don't help because you do say things that are very rude about me and that like just gets into their like
Spectrum and like you just fall with a
Expecting me to be better with you
When you don't do give me the same grace. I I try to crystal though. I'm not
What'd I say about you or something?
I'm sorry if I did anything wrong. Okay, you mad me. Hey, oh wait, this is a real Samman. Hold on
I don't think it's a real one though. I think it's a fake Samman. Let me check
See if he runs. Okay. Well, he's still here. Okay, and I'm done with same man
Chris work. Yo, you you you happen on everybody panel, but mine's chris. Are you a fucking flip flopper?
I don't like with that shit man. That's Sam and your voice sounds deep
What oh what I'm in the morning, baby. I'm not I'm not over excited. What's going on? You don't like my manly voice
I like it. Hey, yo
You know good
I like your manly voice out of here. They can stop playing with me man. Chris. What's up? Where my crystal Maria?
Right here
Chris what's up you joining everybody panel now mom yo Chris, that's you're not a superstar. I'm not because your bitch
Told me that she is gonna fucking make sure that I'm out of your fucking life, okay?
That I'm never gonna be able to talk to you again, right? No Chris will be playing me
You don't take the link you deal with her fuck you fuck you go fucking die
Oh
I don't want to talk to him. Please anymore. What's the way? Whoa. Whoa. Whoa. Whoa. Please tell him
I don't want to talk to him anymore. Can you kick him off the panel?
You can let him on the panel. Yeah, talk to talk to 300 glows Sam and she's
Fuck with Jimmy you went to come see now you fuck with sight you fuck with all my ox, man
I'm your up. Fuck yeah, fuck with Jimmy
He's your out, get it go, Barry. Get out of your up
Yeah, he's you're out. Thank you. Don't fuck around with those people like that
Yeah, what would you mean you said you're my op and so that means you are actively against me
You're my steady you can't hang around me period yo, why you can't say stop
Come the fuck down fight
2025 that's a fancy
I don't even like 300 glow. I'll let him fucking talk to me
Yo, Crystal, how you hoppin' on me like that, Crystal? You hoppin' on me. I don't like that shit
You don't, you hopped on me, you fucking told me
Nah, you, man, you wanna cry on that paddle
Do not, uh, I'm gonna make your
You wanna cry on past that, nah, nah, nah
You wanna hold your chest like you care about me
You don't care what's about me
I'm gonna make sure BB shows all those fucking clips of you trying to get
Fucking beat up remember when beta try to get you to fucking op on me
And I fucking said no. Oh, no, it's fine. It's fine. And then you fucking you tripped on me
What Chris you you hurt me when you went to dinner? No, you don't mean because I didn't give you a fucking you know what happened
Well, you know what happened is that Christine said he was willing to give me 40 dollars
Chris you get me off the street
You lost your fucking viewership
Bitch and guess what? You're gonna lose a lot more bitch. Crystal. Let's forget that pass. Let's think about the future
What we're fucking we're fucking I'm done with you, dude
We're gonna realize why you as Kansas City, baby. Come on relax
You know, you know your career right now, you know, Sam
We gave you a chance to make your fucking way
Fucking shit me lost come on Chris, don't do it me like that
You you think it's funny that this bitch tries to get me fucking locked up every week
Nobody's getting locked up, Chris. Relax.
Then you need it you really I'm gonna I'm gonna fucking. I'm sending it to you. Okay. I'm I'm gonna send it to some
My lawyer and you're part of the Rico case
Chris not the Rico children
Chris are not the Rico Chris. I don't want to be part of the Rico
Yeah, you're gonna be part of the Rico bitch, Chris. Well, let's make it man. So we go relax and we go chill
How about that what kind of what kind of what kind of what kind of what's that shit? What kind of white claws you want, Chris?
What kind of white claws you want, Chris?
Hmm, I don't even drink white claws anymore. So what you doing now? I come in peace Chris. I don't want to argue my mind
Yeah, I'm original papa. Come on, Chris. So, you know, you're not the original papa. Do you not know what papa came from?
Do you not know where I originated it? It came from me, you stupid retard.
Chris, why are you so angry at me? Come on, Chris.
It came from my fucking TV shows. It came from my fucking genre.
Why are you so mad this morning?
Do you want me to cook you a breakfast burrito or look I'm cooking you have no
What I'm telling you I'm so irritated with you
Unless you unless okay. We okay. We got to start cooking
How can we I got to be I think I got be beef on board we're gonna start cooking fucking
an old whore in fucking Florida and we're gonna make sure that maybe her
retirement... how can I get you on my parents? I got a goon in her retirement home
bitch. Hold on, Crystal whatever I got to do to take for you to take... I got a 90
year old retirement goon in her fucking area and is willing to fuck her up.
She yeah, you just respected me. You started talking about my teeth start showing my pictures and guess what?
Like I put on that lip stuff and it dried my fucking mouth out
You beautiful
blonde hair come on Chris you must you was my superstar you could come all
become my superstar I started showing pictures of my like but I was wearing I
wore this lip lip all week I wore the slippy at work all week which I don't
wear makeup when I'm at home like a normal motherfucking bitch and he likes to
It ripped it up
And I just wore that
Like two days ago, and that's shit her
When you're not my superstar do I hurt just be honest do I hurt when you know, but you like to play that but but see
But you like to play that
Right, why don't you play Christine?
And so you gotta talk to me. Look look look we having a discussion
What do you show her botched nose before she got her second nose surgery can eldo show that one
All right, crystal crystal your map has you not
Can we show um her uh christine steve when she only had two?
Um, I'm sure we can
Are you are you gonna stop being mad? Yes or no? No
So what what can I do for you not to be mad no more?
Well, you know what you you have to demise. Oh, well, I have to do what?
Well, you tried to demise people for me, right?
I don't do minds. I'm trying to you wanted you wanted to demise people for me, right?
You didn't want me to talk to people you didn't want me to be you
Fucking said hey, what were you talking to why are you talking to them? So hey guess what bitch?
You got to do the same shit
No, I got a shoe people for you
You want your demise?
Crystal, if I get your demise out,
you gonna take my link?
You have to kill off fucking Christine.
She cannot be in your tracks,
and she's no longer around.
Crystal, you want me to catch a body for her as well?
I don't know.
Crystal, what the fuck?
You have to kill off Christine,
and you have to kill off fucking Lady Bathory.
Whoa!
Minecraft, no, I'm not killing nobody.
What the fuck, Crystal? You evil.
Crystal out with what Chrissy's you're crazy. Yeah, I'm gonna double it up. I'm gonna double it up. Oh
Lady Bathory and fucking Christine or I'm never going to back
Chris you speaking both of you really made a battery out of it. Why you need to kill people?
Because they try to kill me
Nobody's trying to kill you shut the fuck up Chris. Stop doing the fucking drugs
She tried to get me locked up in a loony bin
That's all I don't like about you crystal you be wallowing now you just be speaking stories. You sound like fucking big teeth
Keep telling you stop with all these stories shit you be doing manager
My
It doesn't really want to talk to you. I don't think my phone is shut up. You told about my people
You need to come to fuck down you upset that's not my superstar no more. All right, let's let's demand
Fuck same thing good Chris or your audio fix your audio when you talk to me, yeah
I was trying to kick up dust yelling at me for
Go to clumsy you like clumsy too. I don't like you be sad tripping on me crystal
Are you like clumsy you be fucking sucking his dick
You enjoyed clumsy fucking harassing me. You didn't give a fuck about him saying you want to
Sexually harass me and do all these bad things to me and my family
But when it came to other people you thought it was oh, it said to me it was funny and it was all things fun
right
Go fuck
Well fucked yourself nigga
Yeah, I hope you die a little bit
And you know what in all this this these bad
Fucking or is that you're trying to put off with the fucking bad people? You're really gonna get
Karma is gonna get you God is gonna get you crazy. God will tell you that you are doing bad. Okay, and God
God is never gonna reward you
Wreck her fucking life she's about to fucking fall
What's like that site this is your new channel? Guess what?
Like this is a new channel
Shout to your new channel. Okay. I got I thought I thought I had this already. Why?
I
Oh
They shared a monster you can share the monster if you want. I don't mind. Have you a monster? Yeah, share it share it
Oh suck dick all you want. Well, I would just appreciate
My channel. I mean it's not my mom's. I won't be monetized. It's like
The dick suck the tip Christian Chris why you turn of violence? Yeah, I don't disrespect you like that
I told about something but you did though, but you have
Don't don't violate me. I respect you Christian. Don't try to violate me you heard
Show me some respect nigga
Start playing with me now calm down Chris. I know you're mad thing. Not my superstar. How can we how do you fix that?
You got to shut the fuck up. Stop talking dirty start fucking drinking. We need a break over the drinking alright. I see left
I don't know why she left. Oh
Damn there you go the content
No, she's back. She's back. She's back. Look at you back. Okay?
Crystal
I
Crystal you need to stop drinking
Chris you need to start drinking start talking that you know what you need to stop fucking leaning
You need to stop fucking using people for content, especially your fucking retarded brother
Oh, yeah, I got a retarded brother down. Why are you talking about my brother?
That's crazy. Yeah, he uses retarded brother to like attack you. Well, it's it's kind of sick
Christian you look you signed retarded
Yeah, I am kind of retarded right now. I'm drinking. I'm retarded
I'm leaning right now. I'm leaning on my couch
I mean like this is the cough medicine. I'm sorry
Chris you just let me know Chris you don't want to be my superstar stop stop lying on me. All right. That's you not a superstar
I'm not ever lying on you. I
Don't you tell me how to fill
You fucking
The more you try to tell me how to still somebody's gonna fucking walk up to you and tell you how you feel
Christopher Christopher you was crying on the walk up to you and tell you how you was crying
You keep putting me in bad situation
You keep, you keep putting, you keep putting me in bad fucking ops, you keep giving me
bad ops, guess what my, guess what my ops are telling me, guess what my higher ups are
telling me, guess what my higher ups are telling me, oh not the higher ups, I'm fine don't
worry about it, they got me, he's fucked, I thought we said a higher ups though,
Yeah
They don't like you no more
They go they go they go Christine
Wow, that's not Christine Wow
That's not Christine. Why are you doing that to her? Yeah, that is Christine
Say you look like she has mentally ill and um stalk your ish chat tonight, and she can you are mentally ill
She's a crack or she has a quailude Christine she takes too many quailudes. She doesn't know what the fuck's going on
Her fucking son hates her by the way. He talks about her fucking
Family all the time. They hate her they hate her
He hates her everybody hates her I tell you she tries to fight for like kids rights when she's mean to the kid
Stop lying on her Chris are you discussing a piece of shit?
Well, you can look it up. I got a higher up. That's 90 years old
Ninety years old a higher up in her fucking community
Is it her grandmother? I mean just like this is getting crazy. I got 90. I got a 90
Yeah, like, no, no, it's somebody that hates her, like,
good to your roof is like 90 years old.
And then their grand people came to me and, like, want me to, like, harass.
And I ain't down, dude.
I don't even know, like, she harasses me.
I don't harass her, dude.
Sike, is that what we up or no?
This lab will be up. It's on the panel verse. I'm syndicated there. Yes, keep it up
It'll be up there in spanel verse anyway, panel verse BOD on the wrong but keep your original law so you could get to
Your viewers up, right? Well, yeah, but I'm not monetized. So it doesn't really matter
Well, you got you got that's on your way to get monetized, right? I mean it's just for the algorithm
I don't I was my channel is deleted Sam and so it's like I don't know if I can like
You can re monetize you got to do it with a different email and a different information
You got to separate the channels. You separate this channel with your main channel. No
Yes, it separates the separate. All right. So you guys you come to monetize. I did it
Okay, but did you ever have a channel?
Tell me exactly how you did it stop it Sam here
Cool, thank you. I didn't know
Yeah, as long as you separate with the emails all that like our Google assets like that
When you do a Google assets won't put it as the same Google assets as the main channel. That's how to get you
Because how about like the other ads that you have to create a new ad sensor something. Yeah, okay
Well, you got you got plenty of people to do it for you. You got you got you got your supporters. Okay
On my website I have a website and I have it my my show is on twitch like on the website
And so it's like people can always go to the website and I'll always be like, you know
On something, you know, even if it's I have to get backup channels or whatever, but I have a few backup channels, too
No, I'll get all good
There you go. That's good. That's good advice. Thank you so much
Shut up fucking same and I fucking loved you
You're my love don't die
Crystal one thing I learned love don't die. I loved you dude. No, I don't love me. Don't love me you started saying
Chris say you love me that say you love me and now we could switch it up then
I love you gotta have still love for me if you want me to
Walk around with no, I lost it. It's gone. You don't lose love man
It's not like I lose you sound like KK. No, I'm not
No more dude, I'm not gonna make money for you anymore
Damn
You don't even like girls
That bitch already said that she already had a plan that if I come up there that she's gonna fucking
Just clap me off when you have not
Protected me or said anything nice about me forever. So why would I go up there?
and give you a show
You never used to worry about
I'm never used to worry about collapse relax crystal
Well, you better get people you better get this bitch a fucking enter a fucking right mind
This bitch needs to get in
Stop being jealous say you acting jealous monica
For real
Jealous of what? I don't know what you want me to be see this
This is another reason I will never go on your show. You think I'm jealous of
Are you stupid so are you spazzing?
Because I don't appreciate people calling me fucking and in calling my fucking jobs and saying that I have mental problems
I'm not gonna tell you the whole fucking works. Okay, okay, but I guarantee you
But it's gonna come back on you and guess what and
Ten fool is gonna happen on you and on that bitch
Keep talking
Keep being rude keep fucking attacking one person. I don't attack you Christian
You do though
Keep drinking Christian. I'm drinking water
God bless you, all right
Okay
God bless you crystal, right
Crystal sure
Well, you so mad at me. You was you was crying in past panel about
Being a superstar and I used so mad now like you're not the same. No because you disrespect me
I can't take it no more you hurt me
No, you are me. No, you hurt me
And I wanted people to know how dirty you are
You dirty
And you don't care about people's feelings and no no was right about you. No, no, they say nothing about me
No, no, did say no was it? No. No, you told about me me
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, don't say nothing bad about me. I fuck
Yeah, she said that she
Don't break dude. Don't be don't lie. Oh, no, no, Chris respect. No, no, come up
No, no, don't even come around the community
Let her come up because probably you were disrespecting me so hard
All right, Crystal
She cried to me and it made me feel like very that's why I'm getting emotional thinking about it
Crystal, can I give you a hug Chris? You look emotional
But she cried talking to me saying these people are fucking with you
No, no cry to you and I was saying that they were fucking with my mental like you guys were trying to like
Like confuse me. No, no
And I didn't feel like it was okay, you know, like
like
You guys think it's fine for for people to have like okay
Crystal to fake this give fake disorders on people or what's to have a nice day
I got it. I gotta get ready for my Sunday service. I'm getting I'm telling you